In this course, we'll mainly be using
在这个过程中 我们主要会使用
the AWS Console to interact the different services in AWS.
AWS 控制台 以交互 AWS 中的不同服务
We'll be exploring many different services,
我们会探索很多不同的服务
and most of the usage that will cover and
大部分的使用会覆盖和
consume throughout this course will be covered by the AWS Free Tier.
整个过程将被 AWS Free Tier 覆盖
To take as quick look or through some of the AWS Console,
要快速查看或通过某些 AWS 控制台
you should have a AWS account.
你应该有个 AWS 账户
If you don't already can sign up for one at aws.amazon.com,
如果您还不可以在 aws.amazon.com上报名
and we'll be looking at several different services.
我们会看几种不同的服务
To highlight a few of them,
为了突出其中的几个
this is the EC2 Console,
这是 EC2 控制台
where you go to create EC2 instances.
用于创建 EC2 实例的位置
Looking at the VPC service,
查看 VPC 服务
this is where we'll spend some time looking through VPCs networking,
这就是我们在 VPC 网络上花点时间
and the different options for network access,
以及网络访问的不同选项
both internal and external to your AWS VPCs and networking.
您的 AWS VPC 和网络的内部和外部
We'll also spend some time looking at DynamoDB,
我们还会花些时间看看 DynamoDB
Amazons non-relational database service, and also S3.
Amazons 非关系数据库服务和 S3
Amazon servers for object storage,
用于对象存储的 Amazon 服务器
these are buckets where we can put objects files.
这些是存储对象文件的存储区
We'll be looking at a lot of different options within S3,
我们会在 S3内看到很多不同的选择
the different storage tiers and different components,
不同的存储层和不同的组件
and features that make up S3.
以及组成 S3的功能部件